https://www.jmi.org.uk/privacy-policy/

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998).We will use your personal information to keep you informed about events, news and offers that we think will be of interest to you. If you have chosen to receive them, we will also use your information to provide you e-mail bulletins and other e-mail alerts letting you stay up-to-date about relevant offers.We may also use the information to process any transactions you undertake with us and for internal administration and analysis. We disclose your information to third parties only for providing the above services to you. We do not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties.The type of information we will collect about you includes:your nameaddressphone numberemail addressyour preferences for receiving information We do not store credit/debit card detailsWe will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a “cookie” which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings. We also track click-through links in emails sent as part of our e-bulletin subscription service.By disclosing your personal information to us using this website or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by Jewish Music Institute in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.
TwitterWatch Malcolm Singer’s #Chanukah lecture on #leonardbernstein The Jewish Works | Here: https://t.co/VRB55pwdQ7@magda_biran @SOAS @NLebrecht Always welcome to join usRT @SOAS: Be sure to join SOAS-based @jewishmusicUK tonight for these two special events! https://t.co/IJTp9nZJFZ
Events
JMI Online: Festival des Andalousies Atlantique 2020 13/12/2020																									 - 16/12/2020
Info & tickets
JMI World Tour: A Celebration Of Jewish Music 11/02/2021
Info & tickets
Mailing List Email address (required)
First Name
Last Name
I consent to receive emails from jmi.org.ukBy submitting this form, you acknowledge you have read and agree to our mailing list terms Subscribe Your browser is out of date!Our website makes use of current web technologies. We recommend updating your browser to view this website correctly. Update my browser now »×
